BEKA BENIDZE



PROFILE

1 (+995) 557-96-07-17

beqabenidze9@gmail.com

Tbilisi, Beliashvili st. 8

https://www.linkedin.com/in/bega-benidze-78627b264/

https://beqabenidze.github.io/portfolio/

As a 22 year old ISET student with experience as a programming tutor at Bitcamp, I possess a solid foundation in coding and a keen understanding of JavaScript, web development and related technologies with working knowledge of backend development. My tutoring experience has sharpen my ability to communicate complex concepts effectively and provide deep understanding and constructive feedback on coding practices.

Now, I am eager to direct my technical expertise, adaptability, and

unwavering enthusiasm into a dynamic role within a forward-thinking

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF ECONOMICS

Bachelor's Degree in Economics ISET - International School of Economics at TSU

Website - https://iset.tsu.ge/ 2020 - present

SECONDARY SCHOOL

N 147 Tbilisi State School 2008 - 2020

LANGUAGES

- Georgian native speaker
- English fluent / C1
- Russian fluent / C1

EXPERIENCE

JUNIOR SOLO BANKER / Bank of Georgia

2023 - 2024

company.

- analyzing financial statements
- meeting with clients or other bank representatives
- Processing loan applications and documents related to lending activities

PROGRAMMING TUTOR / Bitcamp

2022 - 2023

- Introduce students to fundamental concepts of frontend development
- Guide students through advanced topics: JavaScript frameworks like React
- Provide constructive feedback on student's code.

REPRESENTATIVE/CUSTOMER SERVICE / DressUp Group 2021 - 2022

- providing customers with appropriate service
- ensuring customers have a positive experience from start to finish
- handling various customer situations with empathy and professionalism

SOFT SKILLS

- Problem-solving
- Resilience
- Time management
- Communication
- Adaptability
- Commitment to work

PROGRAMMING SKILLS

- JavaScript / Typescript
- React / Frameworks & Libraries
- NodeJS
- mongoDB
- Git
- SQL